上个月 为庆祝我们的一周年
So last month,to celebrate our one year of dating bliss,
Dave给我了个惊喜 带我去了 Huey Lewis and The News演唱会
Big Dave surprised me and took me on a Huey Lewis and The News cruise.
第七首安可曲"Hip To Be Square"的时候
Cut to seventh encore "Hip To Be Square,"
Huey把我拉上舞台
Huey pulls me up on le stage.
接下来的事你打死也想不到
You'll never guess what happened next.
- 我的上衣掉了 - 她自己脱的
- My top came off! - She took it off.
不能直视
Ugh! Gross,mom!
- 她风韵犹存噢 - 真的吗
- She's a keeper. - Really?
Huey Lewis他们都直立了
Huey Lewis and them thangs
既然你问起
So in answer to your question,
这是我的咪咪第二次被一堆人看
that was the second largest crowd to ever see my hooters.
那第一次是什么时候
Ooh! What was the first?
- Robert Bork的听证会 - 92年硕士毕业
- Robert Bork's confirmation hearing. - The '92 Masters.
- 你俩说的可不一样 - 等等
- You said one thing,you said another thing. - Oh,wait.
- 这是第三次吗 - 演唱会是第三次
- Ooh,is that the third? - Cruise was third.
- 好吧 这是第三次 - 是的
- Okay,that was the third. - Yeah.
说起出去玩 我们玩点什么好呢
Speaking of things hanging out,how about us,huh?
我爸和Penny的妈妈都在
We've got my dad here,we've got Penny's mom,
大家都在了 太好了
the whole crew. This is great.
是啊 想不通为什么有人觉得
I know. I don't know why anybody thought
你们约会很奇怪
it was weird you guys were dating at first.
你们超般配 像Jay和Bey那么般配
You are great together-- Jay and Bey great.
- 不懂你在说什么 - 她是说Jay-Z和Beyonce
- Don't know what that is. - She means Jay-Z and Beyonce.
不是我在Chesapeake湾的朋友Jay
Not my friend Jay in the Chesapeake Bay...
他在那溺水身亡了
'cause that's where he drowned.
安息吧 Jay
RIP,Jay.
潮水拥你入怀 地狱唤你回家
Embraced by the tide and called home to hell.
不管什么湾
Any-bay...
这么多人 明天干嘛好呢
what are we gonna do with this big group tomorrow,huh?
4对4斗牛?
A little 4-on-4 hoops?
八人欢乐单车 要不舞个龙?
Maybe an 8-person party bike? Chinese New Year dragon?
其实 我们打算带Penny和Dave
Well,actually,we're taking Penny and Dave
去科技馆看"电视机器人发展史"
to that "TV Robots Through The Ages" exhibit... at the Museum of Science.
全是好东西
It covers all the greats.
杰森一家里的Rosie
They got Rosie from "The Jetsons,"
霹雳游侠里的KITT 还有Angie Harmon
KITT from "Knight Rider," Angie Harmon.
那我们四个怎么办
What about this foursome over here,huh?
Jane Brad Alex 我们几个干什么好
Jane? Brad? Alex? What are we gonna do?
舞个迷你龙吗
4-person mini dragon?
听起来不错 不过我们得去割礼
Uh,we would love to,but we have to go to a bris.
- 去什么 - 就是犹太割礼的聚会
- A what? - It is a Jewish circumcision party.
别担心 只有那个婴儿会受割礼
Don't worry. Only the baby gets circumcised.
玩得开心 看好小弟
All right,well,have fun. And mind your groin.
看起来大家都有
Okay,so everybody's got...
安排了 挺好的
got stuff to do. That's-- that's good.
那就先这样 然后再...
We'll put a pin in it, and then-- and then we'll all... get...
等大家有空再聚
get back together w-when-- when everyone's schedule permits.
你看着不太高兴
This is not a great color on you.
我觉得你们总聚在一起挺可爱的
Well,I think it's adorable how much time you guys spend together.
整天黏在一起
You're practically attached at the hip,
像"真体育"里的德国连体妓女
like those conjoined German prostitutes I saw on "Real Sports."
也是举重选手
They're also power lifters.
我不觉得我们黏在一起
I wouldn't say we spend that much time together.
不过是一星期的四五次早餐
I mean,just breakfast four or five times a week before work.
差不多每天小酌几次
And drinks during the day most days.
也没有每天 不过每晚是肯定的
Not every day,but definitely every evening.
新八卦都要当面传达
And,sure,we always deliver news in person.
也许这点要重新考虑下
You know,maybe we should review that policy.
Jane 你知道Max跟谁搞上了吗
Jane,did you hear who Max hooked up with?
一个叫Jorsh的人
A guy named Jorsh.
能稍后再谈吗
Um,can it wait?
Jane 你听说....
Jane! Did you hear what I--
Jorsh亲娘 这真不是闹着玩的
Dear Jorsh. That thing is no joke.
还是不懂为啥你要看我的检查表
I still don't know why you felt the need to read my chart.
人家总说 得看看别人的想法
Jane,they say you should always get a second opinion.
只是我自己的比较恶心罢了
Mine just happens to be gross.
- 是啊 - 说得没错
- Yeah,it is. - You got that right.
但感觉不错
But it feels so good.
<font color=#70DB93>-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org/=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业途径</font>
<font color=#70DB93>-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-  Proudly Presents</font>
<font color=#70DB93>-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: PP DB Gin 校对: Jasmine抱歉让大家久等了 时间轴:有志青年</font>
<font color=#70DB93>-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-  Sync:有志青年</font>
<font color=#70DB93>幸福终点站 第3季 第22集</font>
<font color=#70DB93>Happy.Endings S3Ep22</font>
我们撒谎说去割礼会不会不太好
Are we terrible people for lying and saying that we were going to a bris?
不 我们又不是坏人
No. We're not terrible people.
只是需要时间二人世界
We need some couple time away from the group.
入了这个网球俱乐部 就只属于咱俩了
If we get into this tennis club,it could be our thing.
就像"让爱一切成空"只属于空气补给乐队
Like how making love out of nothing at all is air supply's thing.
害怕扣篮大赛只属于Lebron
Yeah,like how being terrified of a dunk contest is Lebron's thing.
没错
Exactly.
你说得对
You know,you're right.
说谎才能不伤Max的心
Lying is the only way to avoid hurting Max's feelings.
不带他玩他承受不来
Dude cannot handle being excluded.
Max 我们说去墨西哥过周年
Um,Max,when we said we're going to Mexico for our anniversary...
意思是只有我俩去
We meant just us.
走吧 Danny
Come on,Danny.
想不到最后还是带了他
I can't believe we brought him.
想不到他还赢了湿裤大赛
I can't believe he won that wet pants contest at Se?or O'Callahan's.
别担心 去割礼天衣无缝
Don't worry. A bris is a great lie.
我会告诉他我们准备骑马
I was gonna tell him we were going horseback riding,
但我担心不小心以后都得用女鞍了
but I was afraid it would come out that I ride sidesaddle.
您好 您好
Shalom. Shalom!
你们好呀 怎么了吗
Hey,guys. What is up?
我们打算跟你们去割礼
We were gonna tag along with you guys to that bris.
Alex从来没去过 我去过两次但忘记了
Alex has never been to one. And I don't remember my first two.
第二次割礼与其说是宗教仪式
Of course,the second one was less of a religious ceremony
不如说是水上摩托艇惨案
and more of a horrific jet skiing accident.
等下 去割礼为啥要穿得像大小威廉姆斯
Wait. Why are you guys going to a bris dressed like Venus and Jane Williams?
Alex 根本就没什么割礼
Alex,there is no bris.
他们是去打网球
They're going to play tennis.
唯一想不通就是你们为何要说谎呢
The only question is... why would you lie?
- 我可没说谎 - 为什么要骗我们
- Yo,I ain't lie. - Why would you lie to us?
不是我说谎 是情况有变
The facts did change,but I ain't lie.
- 你得说真话 - 别这样跟我说话
- You need to tell the truth. - Don't come at me like that.
- 你说真话我就不这样 - 别这样跟我说话
- Wouldn't have to if you told the truth. - Don't come at me like that.
- 你说真话我就不这样 - 你非得这么说是吗
- I wouldn't have to if you told the truth. - You talk like that,for real?
- 这是诚信问题 朋友间的互信 - 你让我没有安全感
- It's about honesty. It's about honesty between friends.- It makes me feel unsafe.
好了好了 被你们发现了
All right,okay. We're busted.
我们要去一个私人网球俱乐部
Brad and I are joining a private tennis club,
我们没说是因为不清楚你们的态度
and we didn't tell you because we-- we know how you get,
怕你们知道会取笑我们 懂吗
- and we were afraid that you-- - That you would,um,make fun of us. Right?
怕被你们笑
Yes. Make fun of us.
就怕这个 怕被你们取笑
That... was the fear. That was the fear right there.
拜托 这就是我
Guys,come on. This is me.
我当然会笑你们
Of course I'm gonna make fun of you.
现编现卖 哥就擅长这个
I mean,almost immediately,I'm in an area of what time
您的怀表几点啦 土豪大使
is your monocle fitting, Ambassador Goldface Von Cash?
- 别说了 - 这只是个暖场
- Stop. - And that's just first blurt.
- 点个赞 - 不邀请你们实在说不过去
- Love it. - Guys,we would've totally invited you,
但这个俱乐部真的很挫
but it's gonna be really lame.
我们自己都不太想去
I mean,we don't even wanna do it.
只是Brad需要发展下人脉
It's really just a networking thing for Brad.
肯定不适合你
Definitely not your scene.
- 停 听不下去了 - 就是
- Say no more. That sounds horrible. - Yeah.
好吧 结束了找你 如果没被球砸死的话
Agreed. Hey,catch you after,if we haven't killed ourselves. Am I right?
- 别这样 - 好了 世界和平
- No. Don't do that. - Okay,all right. Peace on Earth.
好好打球吧 土豪大使
Enjoy your tennis,Ambassador Goldface.
你也是 土豪夫人
You,too,Mrs. Cash.
真是太搞笑了
Oh. That's so,so funny!
- 我的天 - 我想他们信了
- Good save. - I think they bought it.
他们绝对以为我们信了
I bet they think we bought it.
不适合我们也说得出来 你懂的
Not our scene? You know what that means,right?
那俩暴发户觉得我们不够格参加俱乐部
Those two richies think we're not good enough to hang out at a tennis club.
- 他们真的这么想吗 - 那是
- They do? - Yeah.
这就是朋友渐行渐远的原因 Alex
This is how groups of friends fall apart,Alex.
不久他们就开始过上流生活
Pretty soon they're gonna start doing all this rich people stuff
留下我们这些穷人自己一边玩
and leave us poor folks to fend for ourselves.
- 我们得做点什么 - 对
- We need to do something about it. - Yeah.
让上等人看看底层人民也不差
Let's show that 1% that the other 10% are just as good as they are.
就是
Exactly.
全家出游真开心
What a fun family outing.
- 好开心 - 就是 真好玩
- Oh,what fun. - I know. It's amazing.
从Crispin Glover借来的原版的机器娃娃
They got the original "Small Wonder" robot on loan from Crispin Glover.
慢着 收集机器人的机器人 我说对了吗
Wait. Robots collecting robots. Am I right?
有人要喝饮料吗
Can I get anyone a drink?
我车里有家酿雪梨酒 我去拿
I have a lovely homemade pear wine in the trunk of my car. Let me get that.
不如来点香槟
Well,uh,actually,how about some champagne?
我们有点事想说
Because we do have some news.
我就知道 他们要结婚了
I knew it. They're getting married.
我...去死好了
I... die.
如你们所知 我们都很爱对方
As you know,Big David and I care about each other very much.
然后呢
And?
- 我们年纪也不小了 - 老了
- And we're not getting any younger. - We're a little old.
然后呢
And?
我们准备领养个小孩
We're adopting a baby.
- 啊哦 - 呃
- Oops. - Uh-oh.
看来你俩有点被吓到
I can see that you kids are a teeny bit wigged out,
这么说吧 养育你们的过程很幸福
but listen,we got so much joy out of raising you both,
我们打算一起再感受这幸福
that we've decided to do it again... together.
而且你们也长大独立了
Besides,we're through raising you.
- 你们大了 也不需要我们了 - 是的
- You're all grown up. Don't need us anymore.- Oh,yeah.
不需要我们了
It's over.
所以 你们觉得怎样
So... what do you think?
我们觉得怎样?
What do we think?
简直太棒了
This is great news.
你们喜欢哪种? 非裔 亚裔 还是白人小孩?
What flavor are you thinking? Black,Ayzsh,original recipe?
Dave 你想对这劲爆的消息 说点什么吗?
Dave,you wanna weigh in on this breaking news?
我知道 外表上我看起来是名 禁欲主义"纯基佬"
well,I know on the outside I may look like a stoic "Just For Men" box model,
但是内心里我是很"爵士范儿"的
but on the inside,I'm jazzed.
"爵士范儿" 这词儿再合适不过了
Jazzed. That is the perfect word.
表达了我们的激动之情的同时 还提到了爵士
It encapsulates our excitement while simultaneously referencing jazz,
美国的一种纯正艺术形式
America's one true art form.
所以 恭喜
So,yeah. Congrats.
- 谢谢 - 或者 说的更准确一些...
- Thank you. - Or,more purely stated...
这沙冰太棒了 Chad
Good on ya,Chad.
是你的手艺 兄弟
Like your style,buddy.
- 宝贝? - 嗯
- Babe? - Mmm.
这地方棒极了 特别是更衣间
This place is amazing, especially the locker room.
我是说 刮胡膏? 爱死了 毛巾? 爱死了
I mean,shaving cream? Heated. Towels? Heated.
更衣间的服务员? 更加爱死了...
Locker room attendant? Heated...
我告诉他那些洗涤液里满是 有毒的对羟苯甲酸酯
When I pointed out all of those lotions are full of toxic parabens,
别担心 我告诉他了防治办法
but don't worry. I gave him a thick tip.
恩 我猜到了
Mm,bet you did.
我刚刚吃了杯石榴蓝莓藜麦沙冰
Well,I just had a pomegranate blueberry quinoa smoothie,
我告诉你 如果有一点儿氧化物留在我体内
and let me tell you,if there is one single oxidant left up in me,
我会变成猴子他叔
I am a monkey's uncle.
- 老天 真希望他们让我加入 - 我也是
- God,I hope they let us join. - Oh,me,too.
Brad Jane? 我是Connie Kelly 会员主管
Brad,Jane? Connie Kelly,Membership Director.
大家都说 永远别相信说话用俩人名开头的人
I know what they say. Never trust a man with two first names,
但如果是女士们的名字 这句话就不算数了
but when it's ladies' names,it doesn't apply.
- 噢! - 噢 Connie
- Oh! - Oh,Connie.
欢迎来到黄金海岸网球俱乐部
Welcome to the Gold Coast Tennis Club.
我们很兴奋能够来到这儿 Connie.
We are excited to be here,Connie.
我也很激动能向你们展示这里
Oh,and I'm excited to show you around.
再等等另外两位
Uh,just waiting on two others.
噢! 他们过来了
And oh! There they are.
- 嗨! - 你好!
- Hello! - Hello!
Brad Jane 这两位是 Max和Alex.
Brad,Jane,this is Max and Alex.
- 一个打网球的好天气 不是吗? - 的确
- Lovely day for tennising,isn't it? - Oh,it is.
- 我们能开始了吗? - 好的
- Shall we begin? - Yeah.
- 快点吧 - 等不及了
- Oh,we shall. - Oh,we shall.
所以 我们的父母要一起收养一个孩子
So our parents are adopting a baby together.
不敢相信我不再是他们的宝贝了
I can't believe I'm not gonna be the baby anymore.
这绝对是我现在最可怕的噩梦
This is now officially my worst nightmare.
没错 比跟Jason Giambi 做爱的梦还要可怕
That's right,Jason Giambi sex dream. You're out.
他们都这岁数了 不该再收养孩子
I mean,they shouldn't be adopting a baby at their age.
他们应该腌制葡萄柚 看广播电视
They should be salting their grapefruit and watching broadcast television.
你知道这还意味着什么吗?
And you know what this means?
我们将来要抚养这个孩子
We're the ones who are gonna have to take care of this kid.
我才30 一个30岁的人 怎么能照顾孩子
I'm 30. How is a 30-year-old supposed to take care of a baby?
严格的说 你已经31了
Well,you're 31 if you're a minute,
- 但谁在乎呢? - 好伤人
- but who's counting? - Hurtful.
认真的 我们应该怎么办?
But seriously,what are we gonna do?
这是个坏主意 他们没有用 长远的眼光来看待这个问题
This is a bad idea. They aren't thinking long-term.
他们忘了抚养一个孩子不只是陪 他/她玩耍和抱抱
They're forgetting that having a kid isn't all tickles and hugs.
我很确定如果他们照顾一天孩子 他们肯定会表现得像...
Yeah,I'm sure if they had to take care of a baby for just one day,they'd be like...
不要孩子 谢谢
no,thanks,baby.
没错
Mmm,exactly.
等等 我们需要做的只是询问
Wait. And all we have to do is ask
我们的朋友能否帮照顾 他们的孩子几天
one of our friends with a kid if we can babysit,
然后我们将孩子推到爸妈家
then we bring that stroller meat around Big Dave and Dana
提醒他们带孩子是多可怕的一件事情
and remind them that having a kid is a nightmare.
好主意 把他们吓退缩
Good idea. Scare 'em straight.
就像我们把Max带到监狱吓他那次一样
Like that time we took Max to that prison and scared
所有犯人住在一起
all those inmates into getting their lives together.
- 这是真爱 - 就这么定了
- Tough love. - Let's do this.
这儿就是宏伟的中央球场
And here is the grand dame herself-- center court.
如果这场地会说话 它一定会说 "为什么上帝要这么对我?
Man,if this court could talk, it would say,"Why has God done this to me?
诅咒你 上帝!"
Curses to you,God!"
Connie 你太搞笑了
Connie,you are a treat.
请原谅 稍等我几分钟
Excuse me for just a moment.
不是故意装作跟他很熟
Uh,don't wanna be a name dropper,
但我想我刚看到了库克郡的 副审计官Sheryl Pflimf.
but I think I just spotted Cook County Deputy Comptroller Sheryl Pflimf.
我们关心很好 等我过去跟他打个招呼
We're dear friends. One moment.
Sheryl!
What the hell are you guys doing here你们在这儿干嘛
What the hell are you guys doing here?
旅游散心 考虑加入俱乐部 面对现实吧
Taking a tour,thinking about joining the club. Sussin' it out.
- 没错 直面现实 - 直面什么?
- Yeah,straight sussin'. - Straight what?
得了吧 你们才不是真想加入 一个网球俱乐部
Come on. You guys don't wanna join a tennis club.
为什么? 因为我们打不好网球?
Why? 'Cause it's not our scene?
我们不能成功的挥动球拍
You don't think we're good enough to rub elbows
像你和Sheryl Pflimfs一样？
with you and the Sheryl Pflimfs of the world?
我说这儿跟我俩再合适不过
Well,I say we fit in here just fine.
你? 跟这儿合适?
Really? You fit in?
- Alex 你问了三个人有没有灰色娃娃 - 没错
- Alex,you've asked three people if they have any Grey Poupon.- Sure.
Max 你看起来就像John McEnroe 的胖堂兄-John Mac奶酪
And,Max,you look like John McEnroe's fat cousin, John Mac-n-Cheese.
Max 能否麻烦你们在毁了我们 享受这里之前离开?
Max,can you just get outta here before you ruin this for us?
- 你们才应该在毁了我们的旅途前离开 - 没错
- You get outta here before you ruin this for us.- Yeah.
- 我回来了 - 太好了!
- Sorry. - Ohh!
Sheryl太能说了
Sheryl was a real yapper.
她唯一管不住的就是她的嘴
The only thing she can't deputy comptrol is her mouth.
女人都很能说
Women be talkin'.
话说回来 我想你们都忍不住想 试试在这场地打球了吧?
Anywho,I'm sure you all are probably itching to try out the courts,huh?
你们何不来场双打呢?
Why don't you guys play doubles?
- 我不认为这是个好主意 - Connie! Brad 我们能打双打!
- Um,I don't think so. - Connie! Brad,we can play doubles!
没问题 我给你们安排下场地
Sure. I'll go set up a court for you.
- 我觉得... - 太好了
- You know... - Great.
好吧 规则如下
Okay. Here's the deal.
如果你们赢了 我们将永不 踏入这片场地
If you guys win,we'll never step foot in this place again,
但如果我们赢了 我们有权利选择加入这儿
but if we win,then we get the choice of joining up here.
我们可能就是适合俱乐部的人
We just might be club people.
Max 没人通过网球比赛做决定 兄弟
Max,nobody solves things through tennis matches anymore,bro.
- 我们又不在80年代 - 你害怕了 Arthur Ashey?
- It's not the '80s. - You scared,Arthur Ashe-y?
没人能叫我 Ashy... 永远没有!
Nobody calls me Ashy... ever!
这不是打了我完美无瑕的脸一耳光
That is not just a slap in my evenly moisturized face.
这是对我的洗涤顾问和我的面霜的侮辱!
It's an insult to my personal lotion consultant and my creamist!
- 比赛就比赛! - 谁怕谁
- It's on! - Oh,it is on.
- 谁怕谁 - 谁怕谁
- Oh,it is on. - Oh,it is on.
好吧... 我问过了所有人 没人愿意给我们孩子
Welp... no one would give me a kid, and I asked everyone.
嘿! Allison
Hey! Allison.
你还记得你曾吓了我五分钟说 这孩子是我的吗?
Remember when you thought that baby was mine for,like,five minutes?
你觉得我可以借着孩子五分钟吗?
Do you think I could borrow it for,like,five minutes?
我也生不出一个来
I couldn't get one either.
我被拒绝了太多次 我感觉就像是 Jason Giambi性梦里的Jason Giambi
I got so many "no's," I felt like Jason Giambi in my Jason Giambi sex dream.
家长什么时候变得这么黏 他们的孩子了?
When did parents become so attached to their kids?
如果你爱某种东西 就应该给它自由
If you love something,set it free.
或者借给你楼下的邻居
Or lend it to your downstairs neighbor.
我能借到一把沙龙级别带烘干机的椅子
You're telling me I can rent a salon-grade hooded dryer chair,
却借不到一个孩子？
but I can't rent a kid.
等等 David 你可能提示了我什么
Wait,David. You may just be on to something.
我知道
I know.
为什么在家能做的时候要去 闷热的沙龙呢?
Why do in a stuffy salon what you can do in the comfort of your own home?
不 我是说你能借到一个宝宝
No. You can rent a kid.
我的公关公司一直在付费请 宝宝拍广告
My PR firm casts babies in commercials all the time.
如果我打一个假的拍摄电话
If I put out a fake casting call,
我能找到50个疯狂妈妈
I could get 50 crazy stage moms
- 十分钟内他们的孩子就会在我 办公室门口排队 - 真的吗?
- and their kids lined up in my office in ten minutes.- Really?
永远别低估一颗妈妈为孩子 攒大学学费的心
Never underestimate the lure of building your child a college fund
还能随时用来给你的男友Tico 买一辆ATV
which you can then raid to buy an ATV for your boyfriend Tico.
可悲呀可悲
Sad but sad.
我就说吧
Told ya.
干得好
Good job.
这就像是一个真的拍摄需求
This feels like a real casting call.
不过我很关心等待间的食物短缺问题
Although I am concerned with the waiting room food situation or lack thereof.
我知道我们午餐在节食
Now I know we're butting up against lunch,
但也许你能摆放一个零食碟子
but maybe you could get a mezze plate going
放一些葡萄 或者鹰嘴豆泥
with some grape leaves,maybe some hummus.
什么? Dave 我们没有时间
What? Dave,there is no time.
我们只需要找到这儿最糟糕的妈妈
We just need to find the worst mother here
以及最不听话的宝宝交给我们的父母
and the most rotten,miserable baby and dump it on our parents.
噢 太棒了
Jackpot.
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
他们简直太完美了 开始吧
They're perfect. Just play along.
大家好 Penny Hartz 公关专员
Hello. Penny Hartz,PR.
Dave Rose 产品设计 主要负责两栖鞋类
Dave Rose,PD. Product Design. Amphibious footwear,mostly.
- 不过我们可以晚点再说这个 - 他是我们的客户
- But that can all come later. - Okay,he's the client.
谁是我们这位漂亮宝宝啊?
Now who is this precious child?
哦 他叫Eddie 不好意思 他有点累坏了
Oh,this is Eddie. I'm so sorry. He's a little tuckered out.
不管累没累坏 我们认为小Eddie 就是我们的正确拍摄人选
Tuckered out or not, we think Little Eddie's the right man for the part.
- 真的吗? - 我们只需要带他去隔壁房间 做个试镜
- Really? - We just need to take him into the next room for a screen test
你不在意在这儿稍等的吧?
if you don't mind hanging out here in the waiting area.
实在抱歉 我们时间太紧 没来得及准备个零食碟子
I apologize ahead of time for the lack of a mezze plate.
我们几小时后带他回来 没问题吧?
Okay. And we'll bring him back in a couple hours. That be okay?
我不敢相信他被选上了 我的给他爸爸打个电话!
I can't believe he booked it. I have to call his dad!
得经过他的同意 这是监护协议的一部分
To ask permission. It's part of our custody agreement.
我确定会没问题的 我不想打断他 他在他的毕业舞会上
I'm sure it's fine. I don't wanna bug him. He's at his prom.
宝贝 你听到没? 你是个明星
You hear that,baby? You're a star.
我们是明星
We're stars.
- 是的! - 没错!
- Yeah! - Yes! Yes!
击垮你们!
...destroyed you!
- 我们赢了! - 我们把你们打得...
- We won! - We won your...
我们 赢了!
We ...destroyed you!
屎去吧
Whoopsie daisy.
你不配拿这个
You don't deserve this!
- 亲爱的 - 干嘛
- Honey... - What?!
怎么了
What's up?
除非我们不想加入这家超酷的俱乐部
...is how we would have celebrated
我们才会这么庆祝
if we didn't wanna belong to this awesome club.
我不知道 这计划有点疯狂
I don't know. This plan is kinda crazy.
基本上我们算是绑架了个孩子
We're basically kidnapping a baby.
我不知道办不办得到
I'm not sure I can go through with this.
好吧 没错 是疯狂了点
Okay,yes,it is crazy,
但怎么比得上老爸老妈在这岁数 收养孩子来得要命
but is it any crazier than our parents adopting a baby at their age?
没错 值得一试
You're right. I guess the juice is worth the squeeze.
而且 我们也会在一小时内还回来
Besides,we're gonna be back in an hour.
你还有什么好担心的
What you should be worrying about is that
五分钟后 我们就会和爸妈一起吃午饭
we're meeting our parents for lunch in five minutes,
而操心Eddie刚突然变身成超萌Eddie
and Fussy Eddie here has suddenly decided to turn into Super Sweet Eddie
这不会让他们打退堂鼓
who won't bum them out at all.
上帝啊 他真是超萌的
My God. You're right. He is being super sweet.
- 真想有个像你这样的小弟弟 - 什么
- I wish I had a little brother just like you.- What?
哦 对了这完全违背我们的初衷
Oh,right,that's the exact opposite of what we're trying to do here.
好了 我们只要把他弄哭就行了 对吧
Okay,so I guess we just need to make it cry,right?
我们该怎么做
How do we do that?
喂 喂
Hey,hey.
我哭怎么样 那他就会哭 对吧
What if I start crying? That'll make it cry,right?
你想怎么把自己弄哭
How are you gonna make yourself cry?
我这人生还有什么意思
What am I doing with my life?
连我妈谈的恋爱都比我的好
My mom's in a better relationship than I am.
而我还喷着Shania Twain的香水 (加拿大著名乡村女歌手)
And I'm wearing a perfume by Shania Twain.
喔 还真快
Wow,that was fast.
这些都已经录好了 你只需要按个开始键
It's all cued up. You just sorta have to press "Play."
该死的 没用
Damn it. It's not working.
我骂骂他怎样
What if I insult it?
嘿 小屁孩 只会靠乳房吃饭 你个小傻子
hey,baby. Way to get all your meals from a boob, you tiny moron.
他听不懂的
He doesn't understand words.
你得说得更凶残点
You're gonna have to use a harsher tone.
记住我的脸
Remember my face.
哦 你可能办不到
Oh,you probably can't,
因为你还没有物体恒存性意识 你个秃头傻帽
because you don't have object permanence, you bald bitch!
这是怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
问得好 Trish 聪明
Good question,Trish. Smart.
我刚模仿恶魔在跟小Eddie讲话
I was just speaking to Little Eddie in a demon voice
看他对广告拍摄时的吵闹忙乱有何反应
to see how he'd react to the hustle and bustle of a commercial shoot.
而小Eddie的表现让我感动地都哭了
And I was crying because Little Eddie's performance moved me to tears.
等等 先说你们到这下面来干嘛
Wait. What are you doing down here in the first place?
那先说你到这下面来干嘛 Trish
What are you doing down here in the first place,Trish?
等候室没吃的了 而我饿了
There was no food in the waiting room, and I got hungry.
- 早就说了 - 说真的 你们打算把我孩子带去哪里吗
- Told ya. - Seriously,were you taking my baby someplace?
- 什么 没有 - 那太疯狂了
- What? No. - That's crazy.
嘿 准备走了吗 的士已经等在外面了
Hey,y'all! Ready to split? Cab's waiting outside.
哦 这就是你们说的小惊喜吗
Ohh. Is this the little surprise you told us about?
多可爱的小宝宝啊
What a perfect little baby.
也许我们就该偷这个 我说的是对啊还是对啊
Maybe we should just steal this one, am I right or am I right?
你就跟我回家吧
You are coming home with me.
我要叫警察了
I'm calling the cops.
Trish
Trish.
所以你和Dave绑架了这个妈妈的孩子
So you and Dave kidnapped this woman's baby.
小Dave 是真的吗
Small Dave,is this true?
这取决于你怎么定义“真的”了
It depends how you define "true."
如果是指发生的事情 那是的
If you mean the thing that happened,then yes.
这已经超越底限了
This is beyond unacceptable.
你们究竟为什么要怎么做
Why in the world would you do something like this?
来证明你和老Dave有多不靠谱
Um,to prove how irresponsible you and Big Dave are being,
希望你们已经吸取教训了
and I hope you learned your lesson and stuff.
提醒下 不是你们教育我们 而是我们在教育你们
FYI-- you don't teach us lessons. We teach you lessons.
我不管是谁教谁什么
I don't care who is teaching what to who.
我还是要叫警察
It doesn't change the fact that I'm calling the cops.
好了 女士 可以的话
All right,ma'am,if I may,
我想我了解情况了
I think I know what's happening here.
我女朋友和我想领养个孩子
My girlfriend and I wanted to adopt a child.
让我梳理下
Let me back up.
我是他的爸爸
I am his father,
然后我曾跟这位小姐的妈妈约会
and I've been dating this young lady's mother.
我再补充下 那是在1980年
Let me back up again. The year was 1980.
我还是个风流倜傥 风华正茂的骚年
I was a sexually active young buck with some notions
认为避孕是完全错误的
about birth control that were dead wrong.
好了 他是想说我们想领养个孩子
Okay,I think what he's trying to say is that we're adopting a baby,
而我们的老大们反应强烈
and our older children are freaking.
好吧 这我能理解
Okay,that I get.
当我有Eddie时 我那八岁的孩子完全暴走了
You know when I had Eddie here, my 8-year-old totally acted out.
显然 她是真的理解
Clearly,this one gets it.
所以 妈妈们有共同语言
So,mama grizzly to mama grizzly,
我们放这些愣头青一马 怎样
what do you say we give these cubs a pass,huh?
我是说 他们还只是孩子
I mean,they're just kids.
呃 他们无疑有三十岁了 所以不行
Um... they're easily 30,so no.
- 31 - 好吧
- 31. - All right.
我得像个爸爸那样来处理这事
Well,I'm gonna have to handle this like a dad.
- 开始了 - 够了说一声 Trish
- Here we go. - Say when,Trish.
我正在存钱买沙滩车 所以
I am saving for an ATV,so...
新的还是二手的
New or used?
- 新的 - 好吧
- New. - Yeah.
放进我的钱包
Put it in my purse.
收据发邮件给我吧
E-mail me the receipt.
那么 我猜你们没能加入这间俱乐部
So... I guess you guys didn't get into the club.
没有
No,we didn't.
我知道都是我的错 我很抱歉 我只是
It's my fault. I know. I'm sorry. It's just...
我陷入妄想 你们会奋发向上
I got all paranoid that you guys would move on
然后开始过上流生活 我就再也见不到你们了
and start doing rich stuff,and I'd never see you guys again
因为你们会参加像 电影大开眼界里的各种派对
'cause you'd be going all "Eyes Wide Shut" parties
然后和Tommy Hilfiger比赛泡妞 (休闲服装品牌创始人)
and hunting people for sport with Tommy Hilfiger
或其他上流社会会做的什么事
or whatever rich people supposedly do.
Max 这跟上流生活无关 好吗
Max,it's not about rich stuff,all right?
这甚至也无关网球
It's not even about tennis.
只是Jane和我想过些二人生活
It's about Jane and I having something to do just for us.
我们很喜欢跟你们一起打发时间
Look,we love hanging out with you guys,
但我们也需要一些情侣专属时间
but we need some couple time to ourselves,too.
噢 那你们怎么不早说
Well,why didn't you just say that?
我们不想让你难过
We didn't wanna hurt your feelings,
而且每当有谁想干点啥不带上你
and you sort of freak out
- 你都有点行为怪异 - 不 我才没有
- whenever anyone tries to do something without you.- No,I don't.
呃 还记得Dave患阑尾炎时吗
Uh,remember when Dave had appendicitis?
你揍自己胃部也想患一个
And you punched yourself in the stomach so you could get it,too,
结果却得了痢疾
but all you got was red diarrhea?
我知道了 你们有理
Point taken. Advantage-- you guys.
真的 我很抱歉
Look,seriously,I'm sorry,for real.
我也很抱歉
I'm sorry,too.
谢谢
Thanks.
那么 我们走吧
Let's just go,though.
哪儿也别去
You're not going anywhere.
我想到一个绝妙的主意 能让你们加入这家俱乐部
I've got the perfect plan to get you back into this club.
我想没必要了
I don't think it's necessary.
什么 他想做什么
What? What is he up to?
不知道 他都跳着走了
I don't know. He's got some pep in his step.
- 没错 他看起来好兴奋 - 他会扭转局面的
- Yes,he seemed very excited. - He's gonna turn it around.
- 我想是的 - 不 不要吧 我们又不一定要加入它
- I think he is.- No,no, let's not. I don't think we need to go that far with it.
没起作用 没起作用
It didn't work! It didn't work! It didn't work! It didn't work!
他的主意到底是什么
What exactly was his plan?
没起作用
It didn't work!
所以 Dave和我很抱歉
So,listen,Dave and I are so sorry
我们做了傻事 还对你们收养的事大惊小怪
we acted like idiots and freaked out about you guys adopting.
老实说 这不同寻常
And honestly,it's unorthodox,
但如果有谁能做的话 就只有你们
but if anyone can make it work,it's you guys.
你们会成为好父母 因为你们本来就是
You'll be great parents because you are great parents.
- 最好的 - 听你们这么说真是贴心
- The best. - That's mighty sweet of you kids to say,
但是 现在谁也别想让我们收养孩子
but,um,there is no way in hell we're adopting a kid now.
休想 除非我死了
No! Not on my watch.
逃过一劫
Dodged a bullet on that one.
- 对吗 爸爸 - 是的 长官
- Right,papa? - Yes,sir.
所以在大厅看到小Eddie
So seeing Little Eddie in the lobby
提醒了你们养大个孩子有多难
actually reminded you guys how hard it is to raise kids.
不 事实上在大厅看到你们两个 想偷走小Eddie
No,actually seeing you two in the lobby trying to steal Little Eddie
提醒了我们要有个孩子有多难
reminded us how hard it is to have kids.
没错 而显然 我们还没有 将你们两个蠢蛋养育成人
Yeah,and clearly we are not finished raising you two dumbasses.
老David和我真正想说的是
I think what Big David and I are really trying to say is that
你们两个永远是我们的小宝贝
you two will always be our babies.
那梳梳我的头发 给我做Penny牌巧克力碎片蛋糕
Then brush my hair and make me chocolate chip Penny-cakes.
挠挠我的背 直到我咕噜咕噜叫
And tickle my back until I coo and coo.
- 给最最漂亮的公主梳梳头发 - 挠挠你的胃 好不好
- Brush the hair of a beautiful, beautiful princess. - Tickle your tummy,huh?
<font color=#70DB93>-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org/=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业途径</font>
<font color=#70DB93>-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-  Proudly Presents</font>
<font color=#70DB93>-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: PP DB Gin 校对: Jasmine抱歉让大家久等了 时间轴:有志青年</font>
<font color=#70DB93>-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-  Sync:有志青年</font>
<font color=#70DB93>Happy.Endings 第3季 第22集</font>
<font color=#70DB93>Happy.Endings S3Ep22</font>